Harold Stein Filk Collection
Harold Stein Filk Archive
- Conventions
  - OVFF
    - OVFF 32 Song Contest Winners, 1 copy; Notes: Copy of handwritten item - Theme was Dr ... I Pressume, 1st Place Randy Hoffman, Presumption of Doubt, 2nd place, Gary Hanack, Clan Macrimmon, Third place, Cat Greenberg, Muses. Iron Filker Contest ""George of the Jungle"" - 1st place Andrew Ross - ""George"" also got Audience choice award. Origin: Convention: OVFF 32; genreform: Announcement (Box 9)
      Convention -- OVFF 32 (2016); Announcement
    - Set list for a Dandelion Wine Concert, probably OVFF 32, 1 copy; Notes: Hand written set list includes: Discovery, Circles in the Grain, Come Down, Green Mars, Northwest Passage, Merlin, Dandelion Wine Origin: Convention: OVFF 32; genreform: Set list (Box 9)
      Convention -- OVFF 32 (2016); Set list
    - Pegasus 2017 - Final Ballot, 1 copy; Notes: Blank ballot Origin: Convention: OVFF 33; genreform: Ballot (Box 13)
      Convention -- OVFF 33 (2017); Ballot
    - Pegasus 2017 - Final Ballot, 1 copy; Notes: Winners circled on ballot Origin: Convention: OVFF 33; genreform: Ballot (Box 13)
    - Pegasus 2017 - Final Ballot, 1 copy; Notes: Harold's picks Origin: Convention: OVFF 33; genreform: Ballot (Box 13)
    - Pegasus 2018 Brainstorming Poll, 1 copy; Notes: Blank ballot Origin: Convention: OVFF 34; genreform: Ballot (Box 13)
      Convention -- OVFF 34 (2018); Ballot
    - OVFF 2018, OVFF 2018, October 18-21st, 2018; 1 copy; Notes: White, pocket program style fold-up brochure Origin: OVFF 2018, October 18-21st, 2018 Convention: OVFF 34; genreform: Progress report (Box 11)
      Convention -- OVFF 34 (2018); Progress report
    - First Contact, 1997; The Black Book Band; Dodeka Records; 1 copy; Notes: Origin: @1997 by Dodeka Records, Ltd, 725 Citadel Court, Des Plaines, IL, 60016 Convention: Recorded live during the Brain Weasels tour at Marcon 29, Columbus, OH, May 1994: InConJunction 14, Indianapolis, IN, July 1994 and OVFF 10, Columbus, OH, October 1994.; genreform: Commercial CD (Box 3)
      CD -- Commercial; Convention -- Marcon 29: 1994; OVFF 10; Convention -- InConJunction 4
    - OVFF 9, 1993
      - OVFF 9 - Master #4 Saturday 23 October, 1993 13:15 Hi8, 1 copy; Notes: Box says OVFF 1993 - Wail Songs Convention: OVFF 9: 1993; genreform: Hi8 (Box 17)
        Convention -- OVFF 9 (1993); Hi8
      - OVFF 9 - Master #5 23 October 1993 14:55 Hi8, 1 copy; Notes: Box says OVFF 1993 - Wail Songs Convention: OVFF 9: 1993; genreform: Hi8 (Box 17)
      - OVFF 9 - Master #6 23 October 1993 Hi8, 1 copy; Notes: Box says OVFF 1993 - Wail Songs Convention: OVFF 9: 1993; genreform: Hi8 (Box 17)
      - OVFF 9 - Master #7 23 October 1993 Hi8, 1 copy; Notes: Box says OVFF 1993 - Wail Songs Convention: OVFF 9: 1993; genreform: Hi8 (Box 17)
      - OVFF 9 - Master #8 24 October 1993 Hi8, 1 copy; Notes: Box says OVFF 1993 - Wail Songs Convention: OVFF 9: 1993; genreform: Hi8 (Box 17)
      - OVFF 9 - Master #9 24 October 1993 Hi8, 1 copy; Notes: Box says OVFF 1993 - Wail Songs Convention: OVFF 9: 1993; genreform: Hi8 (Box 17)
    - OVFF 23, 2007
      - OVFF 23 Program Book Program Book, 2007; 1 copy; Notes: Trojan Pegasus cover, staple bound Convention: OVFF 23: 2007; genreform: Program Book (Box 14)
        Convention -- OVFF 23 (2007); Program Book
    - OVFF 26, 2010
      - OVFF 26 Program Book Program Book, 2010; 1 copy; Notes: Color cover with Bride of Frankenstein on a steampunk pegasus Convention: OVFF 26: 2010; genreform: Program Book (Box 16)
        Convention -- OVFF 26 (2010); Program Book
    - OVFF 27, 2011
      - Ohio Valley Filk Fest 27 Program Book Program Book, 2011; 1 copy; Notes: Color cover with cartoon pegasus and lion tamer Convention: OVFF 27; genreform: Program Book (Box 14)
        Convention -- OVFF 27 (2011); Program Book
      - Ohio Valley Filk Fest 27 Program Book Program Book, 2011; 1 copy; Notes: Color cover with cartoon pegasus and lion tamer Convention: OVFF 27; genreform: Program Book (Box 16)
      - Ohio Valley Filk Fest 27 Program Grid Program Grid, 2011; 1 copy; Notes: Programming grid on white paper Convention: OVFF 27; genreform: Program Grid (Box 14)
        Convention -- OVFF 27 (2011); Program Grid
    - OVFF 28, 2012
      - OVFF 28 Program Book Program Book, 2012; 1 copy; Notes: Blue sky cover with pegagus and rocket ship, staple bound Convention: OVFF 28: 2012; genreform: Program Book (Box 14)
        Convention -- OVFF 28 (2012); Program Book
    - OVFF 30, 24 Oct 2014 to 26 Oct 2014
      - OVFF 30 One Shots Lottery Winners Sign Up Sheet, 2014; OVFF 30 (2014); 1 copy; Notes: Performers include: Mark Bernstein, Michael Nixon, Barry & Sally Childs-Helton, Andrew Ross, Marc Grossman, Sassafrass Trickster & King, Faithful Sidekicks, Summer Russell, Lady Mondegreen, Luke Ski, Jane Garthesen, D.I. Blade Origin: OVFF 30, October 23-26, 2014 Convention: OVFF 30; genreform: Sign Up Sheet (Box 9)
        Convention -- OVFF 30 (2014); Sign up sheet
      - OVFF 30 Pocket Program Pocket Program, 2014; OVFF 30 (2014); 1 copy; Origin: OVFF 30, October 23-26, 2014 Convention: OVFF 30; genreform: Pocket Program (Box 9)
        Convention -- OVFF 30 (2014); Program book -- Pocket program
      - OVFF 30 Program Book Program Book, 2014; OVFF 30 (2014); 2 copy; Origin: OVFF 30, October 23-26, 2014 Convention: OVFF 30; genreform: Program Book (Box 9)
        Convention -- OVFF 30 (2014); Program Book
      - OVFF 30 Program Book, 2014; OVFF 30 (2014); 1 copy; Notes: White cover with moose with bird wings Convention: OVFF 30, October 24-26, 2014; genreform: Program Book (Box 8)
    - OVFF 31, 23 Oct 2015 to 25 Oct 2015
      - OVFF 31 Schedule Grid, 2015; OVFF 31 (2015); 1 copy; Notes: This is a very crumpled single sheet, printed on both sides with the programming grid for OVFF 31 printed with the Friday and Sunday on one side and Saturday's full day grid on the other side. Origin: OVFF 31 Convention: OVFF 31; genreform: Schedule Grid (Box 2)
        Convention -- OVFF 31 (2015); Schedule Grid
      - OVFF 31, 2015 Program booklet, OVFF 31 (2015); 1 copy; Notes: White cover with gold Origin: October 23-25, 2015 Convention: OVFF 31; genreform: Program booklet (Box 7)
        Convention -- OVFF 31 (2015); Program booklet
      - OVFF 31 Pocket Program Pocket Program, 2015; OVFF 31 (2015); 1 copy; Origin: OVFF 31, Oct 23 - 25, 2015 Convention: OVFF 31; genreform: Pocket Program (Box 9)
        Convention -- OVFF 31 (2015); Program book -- Pocket program
      - OVFF 31 Program book Program Book, 2015; OVFF 31 (2015); 3 copy; Notes: White and Gold cover Origin: OVFF 31, Oct 23 - 25, 2015 Convention: OVFF 31; genreform: Program Book (Box 9)
        Convention -- OVFF 31 (2015); Program Book
    - OVFF 32, 04 Nov 2016 to 08 Nov 2016
      - OVFF 32 publicity flier from the back page of the program booklet from the previous year Flier, 2015; OVFF 32 (2016); 1 copy; Notes: One sheet Origin: OVFF 31 program book Convention: OVFF 32; genreform: Flier (Box 7)
        Convention -- OVFF 32 (2016); Flier
      - Pegasus concert tech list 2016 Tech list, OVFF 32 (2016); 1 copy; Notes: Hand-drawn microphone map on back of one sheet Origin: OVFF 2016 Convention: OVFF 32; genreform: Tech list (Box 9)
        Convention -- OVFF 32 (2016); Tech list
      - OVFF 32 One Shots - Lottery winners Sign Up Sheet, 2016; OVFF 32 (2016); 3 copy; Notes: Photocopy of original handwritten sheet. Participants include Blind Lemming Chiffon, Juanita Coulson, Kathy Mar, Roberta Rogow, Summer Russell, Jen Midkiff w/Wild Mercy, Court and Country, Mark Ewbank, Lady Mondegreen, Sassafrass + Gary, Lauren Cox, Peter Alway Origin: OVFF 32 Convention: OVFF 32; genreform: Sign Up Sheet (Box 9)
        Convention -- OVFF 32 (2016); Sign up sheet
      - OVFF 32 Pocket Program Pocket Program, 2016; OVFF 32 (2016); 2 copy; Notes: Double sided printout Origin: OVFF 32 Convention: OVFF 32; genreform: Pocket Program (Box 9)
        Convention -- OVFF 32 (2016); Program book -- Pocket program
      - Ohio Valley Filk Fest 32 Program Book Program Book, 2016; OVFF 32 (2016); 3 copy; Notes: OVFF is uncharacteristically in November, on one copy of the back of program lists the wrong year and is crossed out, the other copies are uncorrected Origin: OVFF 32, November 4-8, 2016 Convention: OVFF 32; genreform: Program Book (Box 9)
        Convention -- OVFF 32 (2016); Program Book
    - OVFF 33, 20-22 October 2017
      - OVFF 33, October 20-22, 2017 Program booklet, OVFF 33 (2017); 1 copy; Notes: Neon yellow cover with a pegasus Origin: OVFF 33 Convention: OVFF 33; genreform: Program booklet (Box 2)
        Convention -- OVFF 33 (2017); Program booklet
      - Video Production for Musicians Leaflet, 2017; 1 copy; Notes: Probably a handout from a workshop at OVFF 33 by Kat Sharp. Convention: OVFF 33; genreform: Leaflet (Box 13)
        Convention -- OVFF 33 (2017); Leaflet
      - Promotional flier for concert Flier, 2017; 2 copy; Notes: Bright orange, 15th Anniversary concert at OVFF 2017 Convention: OVFF 33; genreform: Flier (Box 13)
        Convention -- OVFF 33 (2017); Flier
      - OVFF 33 One Shots Lottery Winners Convention Documents, 2017; 1 copy; Notes: Sign up sheet with one shot performer names: Howlin Beagle, Charles Shirling and Brenda Shaffer Shirling, Michael Stein, John McDaid, Mark Ewbank, Katie Roper, Mark Ewbank, Katie Roper, Gary Ehrlich, T. J. Burnside Convention: OVFF 33; genreform: Convention Documents (Box 13)
        Convention -- OVFF 33 (2017); Convention Documents
      - OVFF schedule grid, 2017 Schedule Grid, 2 copy; Notes: Schedule grid Convention: OVFF 33; genreform: Schedule Grid (Box 13)
        Convention -- OVFF 33 (2017); Schedule Grid
      - OVFF 33, Master Schedule, 2017; OVFF 33 (2017); 1 copy; Notes: Single sheet, double sided Convention: OVFF 33, 2017; genreform: Pocket Program (Box 9)
        Convention -- OVFF 33 (2017); Program book -- Pocket program
      - OVFF 33 Program Book, 1 October 2017; 2 copy; Notes: Yellow cover with pegasus, staple bound Convention: OVFF 33; genreform: Program Book (Box 13)
        Convention -- OVFF 33 (2017); Program Book
  - Panopticon West, 1984
    - The Cosmic Filker, 1984; 1 copy; Notes: Yellow cover with singing aliens Origin: in-print (unknown version/edition): https://archive.org/details/cosmicfilkerforpanopticonwest1984 Convention: Panopticon West: 1984; genreform: Songbook (Box 16)
      Convention -- Panopticon West (1984); Songbook
  - Philcon
    - Philcon 2005
    - Philcon 2011
      - Philcon 2011 Program book, Philcon 2011; 1 copy; Origin: Philcon 2011, November 18-20, 2011, 75th anniversary Convention: Philcon 2011; genreform: Program Book (Box 10)
        Convention -- Philcon 2011; Program Book
    - Philcon 2013
      - Philcon Rocket #2, 9 November 2013; Philcon 2013; 1 copy; Origin: 41587 Convention: Philcon 2013; genreform: Newsletter (Box 9)
        Convention -- Philcon 2013; Newsletter
      - Philcon Rocket #3, 9 November 2013; Philcon 2013; 1 copy; Origin: 41587 Convention: Philcon 2013; genreform: Newsletter (Box 9)
    - Philcon 2014, 21 Nov 2014 to 23 Nov 2014
      - Harold's personal schedule for Philcon 2014, Philcon 2014; 1 copy; Notes: Single page printout Origin: Philcon 2014, November 21-23 Convention: Philcon 2014, November 21-23; genreform: Personal Schedule (Box 9)
        Convention -- Philcon 2014; Personal Schedule
      - Philcon 2014 Pocket Program, Philcon 2014; 1 copy; Notes: Pocket format program Origin: Philcon 2014, November 21-23 Convention: Philcon 2014, November 21-23; genreform: Pocket Program (Box 9)
        Convention -- Philcon 2014; Program book -- Pocket program
      - Philcon 2014 Program Book, Philcon 2014; 1 copy; Notes: Glossy Program book Origin: Philcon 2014, November 21-23 Convention: Philcon 2014, November 21-23; genreform: Program Book (Box 9)
        Convention -- Philcon 2014; Program Book
    - Philcon 2016, 18 Nov 2016 to 20 Nov 2016
      - Philcon 2016 Pocket Program, Philcon 2016; 1 copy; Notes: White pocket format Convention: Philcon 2016; genreform: Pocket Program (Box 8)
        Convention -- Philcon 2016; Program book -- Pocket program
      - Philcon 2016 Pocket Program, Philcon 2016; 1 copy; Origin: Philcon 2016, Nov 18-20, 2016 Convention: Philcon 2016, Nov 18-20, 2016; genreform: Pocket Program (Box 9)
      - Philcon 2016 Program Book, Philcon 2016; 1 copy; Notes: Inserted is a tent card with Harold's name and schedule on it Origin: Philcon 2016, Nov 18-20, 2016 Convention: Philcon 2016, Nov 18-20, 2016; genreform: Program Book (Box 9)
        Convention -- Philcon 2016; Program Book
      - The Philcon Rocket #1, 2016; Philcon 2016; 1 copy; Origin: 2016 Convention: Philcon, Nov. 19, 2016; genreform: Newsletter (Box 7)
        Convention -- Philcon 2016; Newsletter
    - Philcon 2017, 08 Nov 2017 to 10 Nov 2017
      - Philcon 2017, November 8-10, 2017, Philcon 2017; 1 copy; Notes: This is a half width white covered program booklet with a listing of events. A larger program book was probably also available with biographies of the guests. Origin: Philcon 2017 Convention: Philcon 2017; genreform: Slimline program booklet (Box 2)
        Convention -- Philcon 2017; Slimline program booklet
      - Philcon 2017, November 8-10, 2017, Philcon 2017; 1 copy; Notes: This is a full sized program book with a colored cover depidting a wizard flying and various other scenes. Guests at this con were Principal Speaker: Seanan McGuire, Artist Guest: Don Maitz, Special Guest Author/Illustrator: Janny Wurts, Special Musical guest; Bed and Breakfast (BIll & Brenda Sutton) Origin: Philcon 2017 Convention: Philcon 2017; genreform: Color program book (Box 2)
        Convention -- Philcon 2017; Color program book
      - Philcon 2017 Pocket Program, Philcon 2017; 1 copy; Notes: White cover, pocket program Convention: Philcon 2017, November 8-10, 2017; genreform: Pocket Program (Box 9)
        Convention -- Philcon 2017; Program book -- Pocket program
    - Philcon 2005, RMW REcord in SS, Philcon 2005; Floating Filk Studios; 1 copy; Notes: Origin: Floating Filk Studios Convention: Philcon 2005; genreform: Burnt CD (Box 4)
      Convention -- Philcon 2005; CD -- Burnt
    - Recorded at Philcon 2006, contact about copy/trade, Thompson, Sherry; 1 copy; Notes: Origin: Convention: Philcon 2006; genreform: Note (Box 7)
      Convention -- Philcon 2006; Note
    - The Philcon Rocket, Issue #2, 2016; Philcon 2016; 1 copy; Notes: Origin: Philcon 2016, November 19 Convention: Philcon 2016; genreform: Newsletter (Box 11)
  - Pi-Con
    - 8 Pi-Con, 27 Jun 2014 to 29 Jun 2014
    - Program Book for 8 Pi-Con, 2014; 8 Pi-Con, June 27-29, 2014; 1 copy; Notes: Grey and white cover Origin: 8 Pi-Con, June 27-29, 2014 Convention: 8 Pi-Con, June 27-29, 2014; genreform: Program Book (Box 9)
      Convention -- 8Pi-Con (2014); Program Book
    - A Slice of Pi - Schedule updates, 28 June 2014; 1 copy; Notes: Updates on who will not be appearing and changes to schedule Origin: 41818 Convention: ?; genreform: Schedule errata (Box 9)
      Convention -- ?; Schedule -- Updates
  - RavenCon
    - RavenCon 2011, 29 Apr 2016 to 01 May 2016
  - Relaxicon
    - Harmuni, the Briitsh Filk Relaxicon, 14 Aug 2001 to 26 Aug 2001
      York University, Britain?
  - Sasquan
    - Sasquan, August 19-23, 2015, 19 Aug 2015 to 23 Aug 2015
      - Sasquan, 73rd Annual World Science Fiction Convention. Progress report #4, Sasquan; 1 copy; Notes: Glossy booklet Origin: Convention: Sasquan, August 19-23, 2015; genreform: Progress report #4 (Box 9)
        Convention -- Sasquan, August 19-23, 2015; Progress report
      - Harold's badge from Sasquan, 2015; Worldcon. Sasquan (73: 2015); 1 copy; Notes: Origin: Sasquan, August 19-23, 2015 Convention: Sasquan, August 19-23, 2015; genreform: Con badge (Box 9)
        Convention -- Sasquan, August 19-23, 2015; Con badge
      - Notes on recordings at Sasquan, 2015; Worldcon. Sasquan (73: 2015); 1 copy; Notes: Handwritten on a pink post-it notes about concerts and events recorded Origin: Convention: Sasquan, August 19-23, 2015; genreform: Note from Harold (Box 9)
        Convention -- Sasquan, August 19-23, 2015; Note from Harold
      - Sasquan, 73rd Annual World Science Fiction Convention, Program Book, 2015; Worldcon. Sasquan (73: 2015); 1 copy; Notes: Fantasy owl on cover Origin: Sasquan, August 19-23, 2015 Convention: Sasquan, August 19-23, 2015; genreform: Program Book (Box 9)
        Convention -- Sasquan, August 19-23, 2015; Program Book
  - Shore Leave
    - Shore Leave '85, 1985; 1 copy; Notes: Origin: Convention: Shore Leave 8: 1995; genreform: Tape (Box 17)
      Convention -- Shore Leave 8: 1995; Tape
    - Shore Leave '85, 1985; 1 copy; Notes: Origin: Convention: Shore Leave 8: 1995; genreform: Tape (Box 17)
  - SilverCon
    - SilverCon 2, 01 Apr 1993 to 03 Apr 1993
      Las Vegas, NV
    - Woad Warrior, 1993; SilverCon 2, Las Vegas, NV 1-3 April, 1993; Dandelion Digital; 1 copy; Notes: Origin: Dandelion Digital ""Building Bridges Through Music"" 3078 Sulphur Spring Court, San Jose, California, 95148 Convention: SilverCon 2, Las Vegas, NV 1-3 April, 1993; genreform: Commercial CD (Box 3)
      Convention -- SilverCon 2 (1993); CD -- Commercial
  - Windycon
    - Windycon 33, 01 Jul 1994 to 03 Jul 1994
      Chicago, IL
  - Worldcon
    - N4-2 Noreascon 2004 - Disc 2, 1 copy; Notes: Mini - 005 fifth box of minidiscs #2 Origin: Convention: Worldcon 62, Noreascon 4 in Boston; genreform: MiniDisc (Box 17)
    - Fri I, 2006; Worldcon 2006; 1 copy; Notes: These appear to be disc of photos, broken down by the name of the photographer, and taken at the Los Angeles hosted Worlcon in 2006 Origin: Photography program at Worldcon 2006 Convention: WorldCon 64, L.A.Con 4; genreform: Burnt CD (Box 4)
      Convention -- WorldCon 64. L.A.Con 4 (2006); CD -- Burnt
    - Fri II, 2006; Worldcon 2006; 1 copy; Notes: These appear to be disc of photos, broken down by the name of the photographer, and taken at the Los Angeles hosted Worlcon in 2006 Origin: Photography program at Worldcon 2006 Convention: WorldCon 64, L.A.Con 4; genreform: Burnt CD (Box 4)
    - Fri III, 2006; Worldcon 2006; 1 copy; Notes: These appear to be disc of photos, broken down by the name of the photographer, and taken at the Los Angeles hosted Worlcon in 2006 Origin: Photography program at Worldcon 2006 Convention: WorldCon 64, L.A.Con 4; genreform: Burnt CD (Box 4)
    - Enclosed DVDs of pictures of the event, LACon 4, 64th Worldcon; 1 copy; Notes: Printed on LACon 4 Stationary, Letter is from Feb 3, 2007 Origin: Convention: WorldCon 64, L.A.Con 4; genreform: Letter (Box 8)
      Convention -- WorldCon 64. L.A.Con 4 (2006); Letter
    - Story into Song: Music Inspired by the works of Lois McMaster Bujold, 9 August 2008; 2 copy; Notes: White cover, pamphlet style, staple bound Origin: Convention: Worldcon 66, Denvention 3; genreform: Commercial Songbook (Box 16)
      Convention -- Worldcon 66. Denvention 3 (2008); Songbook -- Commercial
    - Eclectic II: Prophecies & Lies, 2009; Sassafras; Granoff, Matt; Schiller, Lauren; Palmer, Ada; 1 copy; Notes: This is intended as a companion volume for our last album ""Firebrand"". It collects our favorite tracks from our out-of-print CDs, plus the four finished tracks from ""Sundown"" our ongoing Norse Mythology album project focusing on the death of Baldur, wich we hope to complete in 2010-2011. Origin: Sound editing by Matt (Granoff), Lauren (Schiller) and Ada (Palmer) and special thanks to Brad Smith from the Second Shift audio drama. Convention: WorldCon 67, Anticipation; genreform: Commercial CD (Box 6)
    - Chicon #7, 2012; Chicago Worldcon; 1 copy; Notes: White shiny fold-up schedule Origin: 2012? Convention: WorldCon 70, Chicon 7; genreform: Schedule (Box 7)
      Convention -- Worldcon 70. Chicon 7 (2012); Schedule
    - 53, Intersection, 24 Aug 1995 to 28 Aug 1995
      Glasgow
    - 59, Milennium Philcon, 30 Aug 2001 to 03 Sep 2001
      - Flier with filksong by Benjamin Franklin, 2001; Worldcon. Milennium Philcon (2001); 1 copy; Notes: Green double sided printout Origin: Milennium Philcon, 2001 flier Convention: Milennium Philcon, 2001; genreform: Flier (Box 10)
        Convention -- Worldcon 59. Milennium Philcon (2001); Flier
    - 61, Torcon, 28 Aug 2003 to 01 Sep 2003
      Toronto, Canada
      - TC2 - Torcon Disc 2 - 08/29 - 08/30/03 Ingrid De Buda, Phil Allcock, Mary Crowell 8/31 Joel Polowin, 1 August 2003; 1 copy; Notes: Mini - 001 first box of minidiscs #2 Convention: 61, Torcon: 2003; genreform: MiniDisc (Box 17)
        Convention -- Worldcon 61. Torcon (2003); MiniDisc
      - TC 4 - Torcon Disc 4 - 08/30/03 Judith Hayman, Paul Kwinn 08/31/03 Rhodri James, 1 August 2003; 1 copy; Notes: Mini - 001 first box of minidiscs #4 Convention: 61, Torcon: 2003; genreform: MiniDisc (Box 17)
      - TC 3 - Torcon Disc 3 - 08/30/03 Rosemary Kirstein, Cliff and Carol Flynt w/Ropers, 08/31/03 Mary Miller, 1 August 2003; 1 copy; Notes: Mini - 001 first box of minidiscs #3 Convention: 61, Torcon: 2003; genreform: MiniDisc (Box 17)
      - TC1 - Torcon Disc 1 - 8/28/03 - Spider Robinson Concert 08/31/03 Dick Eney, 1 August 2003; 1 copy; Notes: Mini - 001 first box of minidiscs #1 Convention: 61, Torcon: 2003; genreform: MiniDisc (Box 17)
      - TC 5 - Torcon Disc 5 - 08/30/03 Urban Tapestry 08/31/03 Steve Piziks, 1 August 2003; 1 copy; Notes: Mini - 001 first box of minidiscs #5 Convention: 61, Torcon: 2003; genreform: MiniDisc (Box 17)
      - Torcon 3 Presents: The Columbia Rememberance and Space Celebration, 1 copy; Notes: Contains lyrics and playlist; genreform: Songbook (Box 16)
        Convention -- Worldcon 61. Torcon (2003); Songbook
      - Torcon, the 61st World Science Fiction Convention, 2003; Worldcon. Torcon; 1 copy; Notes: White cover with a beaver in a space suit holding the Canadian flag Origin: August 28-September 1, 2003 Convention: WorldCon 61, Torcon; genreform: Program Book (Box 8)
        Convention -- Worldcon 61. Torcon (2003); Program Book
    - 64, L.A.Con 4, 23 Aug 2006 to 27 Aug 2006
      - LA-1, 2006; 1 copy; Notes: Mini - 011 eleventh box of minidiscs #1 - paper in the box says LA.con IV, 2006 Discs 1-10 (only six discs in box) Convention: 64, L.A.Con 4; genreform: MiniDisc (Box 17)
        Convention -- WorldCon 64. L.A.Con 4 (2006); MiniDisc
      - LA-2, 2006; 1 copy; Notes: Mini - 011 eleventh box of minidiscs #2 - paper in the box says LA.con IV, 2006 Discs 1-10 (only six discs in box) Convention: 64, L.A.Con 4; genreform: MiniDisc (Box 17)
      - LA-3, 2006; 1 copy; Notes: Mini - 011 eleventh box of minidiscs #3 - paper in the box says LA.con IV, 2006 Discs 1-10 (only six discs in box) Convention: 64, L.A.Con 4; genreform: MiniDisc (Box 17)
      - LA-4, 2006; 1 copy; Notes: Mini - 011 eleventh box of minidiscs #4 - paper in the box says LA.con IV, 2006 Discs 1-10 (only six discs in box) Convention: 64, L.A.Con 4; genreform: MiniDisc (Box 17)
      - LA-5, 2006; 1 copy; Notes: Mini - 011 eleventh box of minidiscs #5 - paper in the box says LA.con IV, 2006 Discs 1-10 (only six discs in box) Convention: 64, L.A.Con 4; genreform: MiniDisc (Box 17)
      - LA-6, 2006; 1 copy; Notes: Mini - 011 eleventh box of minidiscs #6 - paper in the box says LA.con IV, 2006 Discs 1-10 (only six discs in box) Convention: 64, L.A.Con 4; genreform: MiniDisc (Box 17)
      - L.A. Con IV Volunteer Bag, 1 copy; Notes: Sturdy canvas back printed on the front with a painting of a spaceman and on the back with the con logo Convention: 64, L.A.Con 4; genreform: Swag (Box 15)
        Convention -- WorldCon 64. L.A.Con 4 (2006); Swag
      - The Official Manual for Space Cadets, 2006; 1 copy; Notes: "only slightly associated with L.A.con IV" cover with frying pan and molecules, spiral bound. It's really a cookbook. Convention: 64, L.A.Con 4: 2006; genreform: Cookbook (Box 16)